<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-01-25T21:02:06+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">hi</title><subtitle>my kewl site</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Memories Of The Universe</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2021/01/24/memories-of-the-universe.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Memories Of The Universe" /><published>2021-01-24T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2021-01-24T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2021/01/24/memories-of-the-universe</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2021/01/24/memories-of-the-universe.html">&lt;p&gt;needles racing towards you as sharp as
doors opening up to an
ocean full of wonder engulfed in a stream of 
conciousness of the world of your own, of the 
father you never would have been, of the
child never allowed to roam, of the
coin and it’s rightful place in the world and of&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;fluff appearing for no reason, of the
fingertips so magical and unique to no one but the imagination of the
creators so far you may only hope to 
dream but they are
here&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">needles racing towards you as sharp as doors opening up to an ocean full of wonder engulfed in a stream of conciousness of the world of your own, of the father you never would have been, of the child never allowed to roam, of the coin and it’s rightful place in the world and of</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Flow</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/02/04/flow.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Flow" /><published>2020-02-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-02-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/02/04/flow</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/02/04/flow.html">&lt;p&gt;In room, dreams &amp;gt; goes backwards.
is in school &amp;gt; goes foreward back home to same room.
eats, reads, throws paper plane.
cover put over him by parent/guardian&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;dis boy sure likes flying
goes from house direkt to school
falls asleep in class.
is woken up &amp;amp; kicked out by teachers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;gets a snap from [redacted]
he forgot his umbrella
jumpy trees move, creepy music&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;stop reminding me that i can move arrowy
gets the urge to call [redacted] sky,
kung fu!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;bidy &amp;gt; let it all go now
recalls everything i recall when i realize i recalled something. -ish
can’t move .. _ .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;birdy is a good türsteher.
peep…..! save the day i mean world i mean bird!! ? !
don’t take it home you fool.!
fun with tree…s
so coincidentally finds animal nursery. please do not put bird in postbox&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;finds own 152 home again?
not much of a challenge
y u hidin? &amp;amp; stop sneeking
it’s your own house….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;none of the deus have good lights
blanki gone big bird water?
swoosh sky bird are you afraid
i am a father now tricky bastard
bread doesn’t contain enough
nutrients to feed a bird +
what’s stopping you
MARRY POPPINS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i can’t believe you’ve just done this
four and twenty blackbirds
promoted to doctor.
pwease no cages
she sure likes animals.
me house is in the wild …
[checkmark] retreived paper plane. ok
and it be raining in me house
so much water hopping
woterplane?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[eye] + [boy]
.. can’t steal his blue bag…
ducky …. MOON
and bubbles. &amp;amp; blue mushroom
too fast for myself
so I took A walk
moon &amp;amp; city so pretty
(having meat. not ours [smiling face] oh
BIG PAPER PLANE boy you gon die
&amp;amp; it’s magic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i want the city as my background
floating island.. or mountain:
OR beach…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;pwease don’t let the teacher be…
me ma…
just a bad dream? or a million
classic door trick.
evil twin ghost. sth ’bout time man.
attention span is evaporating&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;birdy found home after crash [smiling face]
they… stopped ignoring him..
real big trees don’t move
and back to where we started ^__^&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">In room, dreams &amp;gt; goes backwards. is in school &amp;gt; goes foreward back home to same room. eats, reads, throws paper plane. cover put over him by parent/guardian</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Unavailable</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/11/20/unavailable.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Unavailable" /><published>2019-11-20T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-11-20T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/11/20/unavailable</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/11/20/unavailable.html">&lt;p&gt;Of fortitude no word left,
unspoken, accepted in its place of depth
In the corner of your vision lays a lie
You ignore it.. still.. waiting.. patience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A throbbing gut, a pulsating wire
Hooked up to a center you dare not even try to control
For if you do it gets worse and only as you clean up the mess it left behind you realize….
It’s already over, there’ll never be time to process it. Or so you say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Same silhouette, same air, same walk, same place, the same?
Not quite. Never quite. And never. Ever exact.
But always it triggers, for only one day it might not.
You will be forgiven and you will have done what was necessary for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what is necessary?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Of fortitude no word left, unspoken, accepted in its place of depth In the corner of your vision lays a lie You ignore it.. still.. waiting.. patience.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bounded</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/14/bounded.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bounded" /><published>2019-07-14T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-07-14T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/07/14/bounded</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/14/bounded.html">&lt;p&gt;looking for something in a place abandoned long ago
opened secret boxes, they are to be buried
vulnerabilities, only ever masked
eternally, by themselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;forest of possibilities, unavoidable
over earth and under heart a layer, no sights can be erased
rememberance of sea
grand ending (only scripted)
end of passage, or rights, although they had not been granted?
trust, not preserved&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">looking for something in a place abandoned long ago opened secret boxes, they are to be buried vulnerabilities, only ever masked eternally, by themselves.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Reading Into Negativity</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/06/reading-into-negativity.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Reading Into Negativity" /><published>2019-07-06T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-07-06T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/07/06/reading-into-negativity</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/06/reading-into-negativity.html">&lt;p&gt;“thoughts justify feelings justify thoughts justify actions” Hm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An example:
You’re someone with a fairly loose schedule, except that thursday evenings tend to be your /go out with Steve to an art gallery/ dates. You might presume that other friends of yours know about this as you’ve mentioned it occasionally and have cancelled on other thursday events because of it in the past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now it is the beginning of a new week, let’s say Tuesday. A friend group of yours has decided to go out for dinner on Thursday, which they agreed upon over the weekend. You weren’t involved and don’t know about this yet. You don’t find out about it until it comes up during a conversation with a friend who is part of said friend group.
Now you – as one does – begin to think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What possible reasons could there be that they didn’t invite me to go out with them?
Surely they must not want me there. Otherwise they would have asked me, right?
Or maybe they don’t want to spend time with me anymore in general. Maybe they don’t want me to be a part of the group anymore. Maybe I did something to upset them. Maybe I’ve changed in ways they don’t like. Have I been ignoring anyones messages lately? What if I forgot someones birthday? Oh God, what if one of them is celebrating theirs on Thursday and I’m not invited because I forgot about it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…..Really? The possibilities are endless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now it could be that you’re someone who is aware of these thought patterns. And you might try to come up with rational reasons that could lift you out of this cycle.
But what if those backfire, too?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What if “Maybe they didn’t ask me because they already know I have plans on thursday”
leads to “But maybe they knew I had plans with someone else and purposefully chose thursday, so I couldn’t come.” Or
“Maybe they wanted to go to a restaurant, that only serves dishes I don’t like.” leads to
“But maybe they purposefully chose a restaurant like that so that even if I find out about it and did have time, I can’t join.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now since we happen to be in an imaginary situation. We can easily stop.
Take a deep breath. And think about what the hell we’re doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon hearing that friends planned something without us, we got upset. We felt left out. This is a valid and human response. But we don’t genuinely acknowledge that. Instead we try to find a way to get rid of it as quickly as possible. To do that we want to find a reason for our misery, something we can point at and say “Hah, I’ve found you! You’re the reason I’m feeling bad even though I should be feeling fine!” hoping that this discovery magically drowns the emotion. But that’s just not how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So maybe, instead of looking for the endless possible reasons and explanations for people’s actions, we could accept that the situation is as it is. People do what they do. And as said before, we’re still allowed to feel and react honestly. The option to communicate that authentically still remains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh you’re going out on thursday, that’s a shame I would like to have joined.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">“thoughts justify feelings justify thoughts justify actions” Hm.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Contract</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/04/a-contract.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Contract" /><published>2019-07-04T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-07-04T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/07/04/a-contract</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/04/a-contract.html">&lt;p&gt;stuck to you like gum like glue
is it now a part of you too?
it didn’t even cross the line,
just blurred, smeared, all over time
an instinct now, a reflex born out of the illusionary need
to not be alone, not be a part, to,
to…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;to not be.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">stuck to you like gum like glue is it now a part of you too? it didn’t even cross the line, just blurred, smeared, all over time an instinct now, a reflex born out of the illusionary need to not be alone, not be a part, to, to…</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dance To Distance</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/05/02/dance-to-distance.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dance To Distance" /><published>2019-05-02T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-05-02T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/05/02/dance-to-distance</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/05/02/dance-to-distance.html">&lt;p&gt;A fog, laying it’s fingers over your shoulder
lifting you up and away as you try to move closer
In your place taking a stand
telling you it’s all over&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;but it’s not.
Not enough.
not enough time.
not enough space.
not enough happy memories that you’ll leave in this place.
not enough treasured
not enough fought.
no.
too much.
too much buried
too much forgotten
too much taken out of context
and too much run to the rotten core of mind&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;paranoia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;a lightWave. (pleon)
no strings attached?
as if!
pulling you in?
you wish!
it’s doing it’s best, dragging you out
drugging the hell out of you until you cannot shout
but you’re thankful.
because this time
it’s not enough
it can’t go on forever
no trap
pull yourself together
most importantly.
make it your own
you’ll see once it’s a part of your reality
you’ll be yourself once again
you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A fog, laying it’s fingers over your shoulder lifting you up and away as you try to move closer In your place taking a stand telling you it’s all over</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Selbstgespraeche Sind Super Genial</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/01/28/selbstgespraeche-sind-super-genial.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Selbstgespraeche Sind Super Genial" /><published>2019-01-28T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-01-28T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/01/28/selbstgespraeche-sind-super-genial</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/01/28/selbstgespraeche-sind-super-genial.html">&lt;p&gt;Wie bin ich nun auf dieses spannende Thema gekommen?
Natürlich während eines gerade geführten Selbstgespräches!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ich werde mein bestes geben nicht allzu langweilig und sachlich zu klingen, denn mir ist Thema ist mir wichtig.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Man stelle sich vor ein kleines 10-jähriges Kind kommt jeden Tag nach der Schule in eine menschenleere Wohnung. Was möge es nun tun? Rumtoben, singen, spielen, fernschauen.. die Möglichkeiten sind endlos! Aber für mich gab es damals nichts besseres als 2 Stunden lang hin-und-herzugehen und die Luft mit wirren Gedanken vollzumüllen bis ich meiner Selbst zuleide war und mich in mein Zimmer begab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unglaublich aber wahr: Manchmal passieren im Leben Dinge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Es gibt einfach Sachen die halt auftreten und wie der Mensch so ist, macht er sich Gedanken darüber, diese können welche sein, die man anderen nicht mitteilen mag, oder die man erst durchkauen muss bevor man weiß wie man wirklich selber dazu steht, oder man wünscht sich sogar sie einem bestimmten Menschen zu sagen nur dieser ist momentan nicht erreichbar. Und noch viel mehr Gründe existieren, warum man nun mal seine Gedanken für sich behält. Letztenendes ist das auch egal. Wichtig aber ist, dass mit ihnen umgegangen wird.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Die meisten kennen das Gefühl wenn man sich Nachts ins Bett legt und nichts weiter tun möchte als schlafen, aber dann – Kurze Werbeunterbrechen ich mag anscheinend Analogien (Metaphern? metaphorische Analogien? irgendwas passt da nicht aber bear with me) einfach zu sehr: Jeder hat einen PC (=Gerhin). Über Jahre hinweg sammelt man Dateien (= Erinnerungen, Gedanken, Gefühle,.. so was eben). Diese werden einfach immer auf dem Desktop gespeichert, wo unter anderem auch eine ausführbahre Datei namens Schlafen.exe liegt. Wenn man nun nie die Zeit nimmt um seine Dateien auzusortieren und der Desktop überläuft kann es durchaus mal schwer fallen an die Schlafen.exe Datei zu gelangen! Was darauf folgt ist klar, man muss sich erst durch den Schla­mas­sel durchkämpfen und das ist ärgerlich.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naja und die Lösung des Problems? Liegt eventuell im Titel.
Eine beliebte alternative sind Tagebücher aber die werden üblicherweise schnell verworfen. Nicht zu Unrecht, denn dort besteht auch die Gefahr, dass jemand die ließt.. wie gruselig.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anderes Thema:
Eigentlich nicht, aber andere Richtung:
Direkt und Kurz:
Leute finden Selbstgespräche komisch. Oder sie finden Leute, die Selbstgespräche führen komisch. Ich glaube es könnte daran liegen, dass Selbstgespräche oft in Verbindung gesehen werden “psychisch krank”* zu sein. Ich kann mir vorstellen, dass beispielhaft an Personen mit Psychosen bzw. genauer auditiven oder visuellen Halluzinationen, welche mit diesen in Form von Gesprächen interagieren, gedacht wird**.
Unabhängig davon, ist es Schade, dass sich dieser Handlung obwohl sie nicht nur harmlos, sondern auch sinnvoll ist, so entgegengestellt wird.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Selbstgespräche (wie Mediation) sind ein Mittel um sich mehr auf einen selbst verlassen zu können. Es heißt nicht, dass man sich nie wieder anderen zuwendet und alles für sich behält. Ganz im Gegenteil! Außenperspektive bringt unglaublich viel, aber nur wenn man einen Vergleich dazu hat, welchen man erst durch eine eigene Perspektive erreicht. Das heißt: seine Gedanken und Gefühle anerkennen und hinnehmen wie sie sind, egal wie schräg oder nervig, sie sind nun einmal da und dafür kann man nichts. Wofür man aber etwas kann, ist wie man mit ihnen umgeht und da ist Vergebung und Akzeptanz sehr wichtig.***
Doch das gelingt erst, wenn man sich derer bewusst ist, durch das Aussprechen oder zumindest aktive Wahrnehmen der Gedanken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allgemein aber gelten beim Selbstgespräch keine Regeln, es gibt kein richtig oder falsch. Und nur weil es im Selbstgesräch vorkam, heißt nicht, dass man es nicht noch 120 mal wiederholen darf. Genau das sollte man, vor allem für Tiefgründigeres. Für den moment ist es aber gut und ausreichend und für allgemeines Wohlbefinden wichtig denn dazu gehören eben auch die einzelnen Momente.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Es gilt also ausprobieren und erkennen wie sehr was einem hilft, und wenn etwas nicht passt, nicht aufgeben sondern die Ursache finden. Sich selbst als Gesprächspartner gegenüberzustehen kann schon Angst einflößend sein, zumal wir oft viel kritischer uns Selbstgegenüber sind als anderen. Also sollte man darauf achten, dass das “gegenüber-Selbst” dieselbe hilfsbereite, aufgeschlosse und liebevolle Seite zeigt, die auch für andere da ist, die man liebt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allein dieser Post ist eine Art Selbstgespräch. Relevant ist jetzt bloß wie leicht ich die Schlafen.exe Datei finde und nachdem der Text geringfügig lang geworden ist, ich also ziemlich viel durchkämmt habe, geht das (hoffentlich) entsprechend schnell. Gute Nacht.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gänsefüßchen wurden bewusst gesetzt, aber den Grund erläutere ich eventuell ein ander mal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;** Ich möchte beiläufig etwas anmerken:
Dieses Verhalten wird hin und wieder als “schizophren” bezeichnet, jedoch tun solche Halluzinationen nicht umbedingt mit Schizophrenie einhergehen.
Auch ist manchmal von einer “gespaltenen Persönlichkeit” die Rede, welches in erster Linie nichts mit Schizophrenie zu tun hat und zudem ein fehlerhafter Ausdruck ist, der korrekterweise dissoziative Identitätsstörung heißt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*** Diesen Paragraphen werde ich wohl einige male umschreiben. Eigentlich war ich gar nicht auf Selbstliebe hinaus, es ist zwar wichtig und gut! Aber eins nach dem anderen… hm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ich nenne diese Version jetzt mal meine “Rohfassung” die ich eigentlich nicht abschicken will, aber wenn ich es nicht jetzt tue verkümmert sie für immer in der “Entwürfe” Abteilung und das wär mir dann doch zu Schade.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Wie bin ich nun auf dieses spannende Thema gekommen? Natürlich während eines gerade geführten Selbstgespräches!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">#neuralmuellproduction</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/12/01/neuralmuellproduction.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="#neuralmuellproduction" /><published>2018-12-01T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2018-12-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/12/01/#neuralmuellproduction</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/12/01/neuralmuellproduction.html">&lt;p&gt;Created Dec 1st, 2018. Last revised Jul 7, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Die Zermelo-Fraenkel-Mengelehre lehrt uns, dass eine Maus (das Tier?) keine Menge sei.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maschinen behaupten: “Das Gegentail!”. So begann nun die Umdefinition und gleichortige Produktion des begriffsstutzigen Terminuses “Maus” zu “Haut das biologische Objekte enthält”.
Fällt doch nicht sofort ein Makel ins Auge? Natürlich, es ist immernoch keine Menge, Es ist Zimt. Ganz ohne weitere Definitionen von biologische Substanzen, welche aus weiteren Untersubstanzen bestehen und wiederum auseinander genommen werden müssten. Schlussendlich landed man, wie es so üblich ist, bei den Atomen. Doch man darf sich nicht in die Irre führen lassen, das Ende ist noch lange nicht erreicht und abermals man sich versieht tauchen die tiefgründigerereren Probleme auf.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.1 Beispiele:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Grenzziehung. (Plastikverpacking, Haut, Fell.. ?)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In der Eventualität der Vernachlässigbarkeit dieser Probleme sticht eine überarbeitete Ausgabe eines “Das Weitere Problem” durch die Zeitschrift: Ist es überhaupt möglich für eine Maus (oder ein Corallochytrium limacisporum für die Non-Nice-Friends) alle Eigenschaften aufzuzählen? Wie lässt sich das auf einen beliebigen Menschen übertragen? Hierbei sind persönlichkeitsbezogene, auf einen Aussenstehenden, wirkende Eigenschaften gemeint.
Nehme mal zunächst nur die Gruppe der engsten Freunde, diese zählen alle Eigenschaften für den Betreffenden auf. Nehme nun eine fremde Person hinzu und nehme additional an, dass dieser in der Lage ist eine weitere Eigenschaft anzuzführen. Dessen Betätigung verlangt man, bis die gesamte Menschheit “aufgebraucht” ist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jetzt wurde von allen nichtgewählten Menschen 10 Eigenschaften genannt, das bei sehr grober Rundung 80 Milliarden, nicht notwendigerweise paarweise veschiedenen Eigenschaften ergeben für diesen einen Mensch.
Nun ist aber noch zu beachten, dass in den verschiedenen Sprachen Begrifflichkeiten existieren, wessen kein gleichbedeutendes deutsches Wort entspricht.
Zusätzlich hat, je nachdem in was für einer Umgebung man aufgewachsen ist (Kultur, Land, Klima usw.) eine Auswirkung darauf, wie man andere Menschen sieht. Überträgt man diesen Sachverhalt auf unsere Situation so erhält man von fremden Menschen eine ganz andere Palette von Eigenschaften, die den guten Freunden des Menschen wahrscheinlich als “falsch” empfunden würden.
Um auf den Punkt dieser Überlegungen zu kommen: ich denke nicht das ein Mensch in der Lage wäre von allen anderen Menschen auf der Erde so viele verschiedene Eindrücke zu erzeugen, dass dieser letztenendes mit allen Eigenschaften, die es in allen Sprachen der Welt gibt benannt zu werden. Einige stellen sich vielleicht die Frage ob es überhaupt wichtig wäre zu bedenken was all diese Fremden von einem denken. Darauf antworte ich ganz klar: unsere Wirkung auf Andere, unsere vielen Facetten ist selbstverständlich ein wichtiger Teil unserer Persönlichkeit.
Demnach behaupte ich, dass wir gar nicht soweit entfernt davon sind alles Menschen zu sein mit sehr.. sehr vielen Eigenschaften.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Manfred, ich bin [Auflistung von 79 Milliarden Eigenschaften] schönen Tag noch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;#RandomWörterAneinanderhängenErgibtZusammenÜberraschenderweiseKeinenSinn!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;… eine Frage bleibt aber noch: Sind Die Echt?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Created Dec 1st, 2018. Last revised Jul 7, 2019.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Fairytale Never Told</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/29/a-fairytale-never-told.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Fairytale Never Told" /><published>2018-10-29T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2018-10-29T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/10/29/a-fairytale-never-told</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/10/29/a-fairytale-never-told.html">&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time there was a simple minded being. In fact, this being was so simple that it lacked any mental capacity to understand why other beings just… did things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This very being would go into the woods 4 times a week, having the time of its life, utilizing it’s bodily functions to the max, inspecting all the different types of mushrooms, leaves, bushes and plants it could find, taking notes, applying its elaborate marking system to determine only those it deemed worthy of………..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;later throwing them into a river?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now you need to catch yourself. Why did it do that? Why repeat the same type of actions with only small time intervals inbetween? Why all the preperation, use of energy and creativity for it all to eventually go down the drain (not quite literally, but close enough).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, the answer is simple. Because it is fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rather than being consumed by doubts each time it was about to embark on another mission. Wondering whether or not it would even find anything of interest this time around. Or especially on those particularly rainy and miserable days, being so frustrated with the task that it would want to quit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would focus only on how satisfying the process is, because it had payed attention to its own desires, minimized external tasks that didn’t match them and quickly recovered from setbacks by accepting them, embracing the challenges and using them as opportunities to evolve.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Once upon a time there was a simple minded being. In fact, this being was so simple that it lacked any mental capacity to understand why other beings just… did things.</summary></entry></feed>